ssis-suzhou.net 2016-12-15

# Suzhou Singapore International School: Privacy Policy

Suzhou Singapore International School respects the privacy of all who visit our website [www.ssis-suzhou.net](http://www.ssis-suzhou.net/), subscribe to our newsletters, submit forms, and/or contribute to our school with money, time or information.  Through the website we only collect personal information such as name, e-mail address, phone number, etc. when voluntarily submitted by a visitor. Your personal information will never be sold, leased, rented, or otherwise disclosed in any manner to any Entity without your prior consent unless otherwise required by law or as may be necessary as part of a regulatory compliance, or to protect SSIS and its users’ legal rights and public security and interests in emergency.

Please be aware that Suzhou Singapore International School is not responsible for the privacy policy of any other web site. Some links on Suzhou Singapore International School's website will take you to another party's website, we encourage you to be aware when you leaving our site and confirm the privacy policy of another website in advance. This privacy policy only applies to information collected while on Suzhou Singapore International School’s website.

## Cookies

This web site may use cookies in order to customize your experience.  Cookies are used to manage your browsing session with the web site (e.g. - to keep you "logged in" as you move from page to page if you have logged in).  Cookies may be used for the purpose of tracking page visits and other aggregate site statistics.  These cookies do not contain any identifiable personal information and are only used to improve the functionality of our site and your experience while on our site.

## Copyright

Text, images, videos, documents, and any other electronic materials and media available on Suzhou Singapore International School’s web site are available as a resource to the public and are the sole property of Suzhou Singapore International School and are protected by copyright. The reproduction, redistribution, and/or exploitation of any of these materials are prohibited without express, prior written consent from Suzhou Singapore International School.

All users agree that all content and data, particularly any telephone numbers, email addresses, postal addresses or other information contained in the directories of the website, is restricted to the personal use of authorized visitors only.  The commercial use of information in this website is strictly prohibited.  Users agree not to copy, post, email or otherwise transmit any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising or promotional materials.    
Suzhou Singapore International School reserves the right to limit, restrict, or terminate the use of the website by any individual person or party with or without notice at any time. 

We may modify this privacy policy time to time and shall update it on our website. We encourage you to read our privacy policy each time when you visit our website.

If you have any questions please contact us at [information@ssis-suzhou.net](mailto:information@ssis-suzhou.net) .
